You said you intended to recognise England's exit from the EU
and that to do that, we very sadly needed to reform Europe.
But you took heed not to explain how you would do it.
The only thing we've heard until now is that Mr Schäuble said that
to him, Europe's future development had to go through an even more severe
control of nation states' budgets
and of the social rules
that are destroying our societies to the benefit of capital.
I think the Europe that was built is a Europe of social violence,
as we can see it in each country everytime a posted worker
steals the job of a local worker.
A Europe of political violence as we saw it in Cyprus and Greece.
A Europe of war violence, as the war you are preparing against Russia.
This is insane!
Let me repeat what the peoples of Europe tell you all the time:
this Europe has to be changed to the benefit of human beings
or we will all leave it, because no one wants to live in such a union any longer
if it opposes everything people do for their life or that of their children.
Until then, the truth is that we must either change this Europe or leave it.
You have to hear this lesson.
No, the citizens of Great-Britain are not racists or xenophobes.
Voting 'no' does not mean voting for war and against Europe.
It is the opposite.
The vote of British citizens, like the vote of the French in 2005, is a vote in favor of the union of peoples,
for peace and social coordination.
But you don't want that!